A Guide to the Joseph Francis Fletcher Papers (1931-1991)
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Kit to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 Nobember 26 (Box-folder 002:036)
- Leverett Saltonstall to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 November 29 (Box-folder 002:037)
- Ralph Harper to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 November 30 (Box-folder 002:038)
- Mrs. E. R. Hatfield to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 December 2 (Box-folder 002:039)
- Fleming James to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 December 4 (Box-folder 002:040)
- Paul Ramsey to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 December 9 (Box-folder 002:041)
- Dirk Struik to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 December 12 (Box-folder 002:042)
- Fletcher Eaton to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 December 13 (Box-folder 002:043)
- [Hette] de Forest to Joseph Fletcher, 1954 December 28 (Box-folder 002:044)
- E[ ] Koyden to Joseph Fletcher, [1954] (Box-folder 002:045)
- G. Clare Backhurst to Gabriel Farrell, 1955 January 4 (Box-folder 002:046)
- Leonard P. Wittlinger to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 January 14 (Box-folder 002:047)
- F. W. Dillistone to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 January 20 (Box-folder 002:048)
- J. Brooke Mosley to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 February 4 (Box-folder 002:049)
- A. L. Byron-Curtiss to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 February 9 (Box-folder 002:050)
- Allen W. Clark to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 February 9 (Box-folder 002:051)
- Ed Turner to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 February 16 (Box-folder 002:052)
- F. W. Dillistone to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1955 February 18 (Box-folder 002:053)
- A. L. Byron-Curtiss to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 February 19 (Box-folder 002:054)
- [Cyril] Hudson to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 February 22 (Box-folder 002:055)
- F. Randall Williams to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 February 25 (Box-folder 002:056)
- John C. Agnew to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 February 28 (Box-folder 002:057)
- A. L. Byron-Curtiss to [Joseph Fletcher], 1955 February (Box-folder 002:058)
- [Richard Morford] to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 March 2 (Box-folder 002:059)
- Jack to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 March 3 (Box-folder 002:060)
- Rumsey Ellis to [Joseph Fletcher], 1955 March 4 (Box-folder 002:061)
- H[ershell Johnson] to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 March 8 (Box-folder 002:062)
- John W. Darr, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 March 14 (Box-folder 002:063)
- E[ ] Dwight Jones to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 March 21 (Box-folder 002:064)
- Dudley Weinberg to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 4 (Box-folder 002:065)
- Orlo Strunk, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 11 (Box-folder 002:066)
- Robert A. Preston to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 13 (Box-folder 002:067)
- Dick Strong to Joseph Fletcher, 1955april 14 (Box-folder 002:068)
- K. Chug[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 19 (Box-folder 002:069)
- Elton R. Dickson to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 20 (Box-folder 002:070)
- Jane Fletcher to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 22 (Box-folder 002:071)
- Lulu Hardridge Trump to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 27 (Box-folder 002:072)
- Eugene C. Gerhart to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 29 (Box-folder 002:073)
- Jerry to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 April 29 (Box-folder 002:074)
- Hette de Forest to Forrest and Joseph Fletcher, 1955 May 1 (Box-folder 002:075)
- William J. Clark to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 May 2 (Box-folder 002:076)
- [Henry?] to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 May 13 (Box-folder 002:077)
- A. L. Byron-Curtiss to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 May 19 (Box-folder 002:078)
- Jean Laffitte to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 May 20 (Box-folder 002:079)
- Ewell W. Hatfield to Forrest Fletcher, 1955 May 26 (Box-folder 002:080)
- Leon Salzman to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 June 4 (Box-folder 002:081)
- A. L. Byron-Curtiss to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 June 8 (Box-folder 002:082)
- George H. Williams to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 June 9 (Box-folder 002:083)
- Jean Laffitte to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 June 10 (Box-folder 002:084)
- Ralph Lord Roy to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 July 12 (Box-folder 002:085)
- Paul Van Buren to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 July 14 (Box-folder 002:086)
- [Forrest Fletcher] to Ruth and Ewell, 1955 July 23 (Box-folder 002:087)
- Edward to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 July 27 (Box-folder 002:088)
- William M. Hogue to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 September 6 (Box-folder 002:089)
- William B. Daniels to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 September 9 (Box-folder 002:090)
- Jhm [Jim?] to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 September 12 (Box-folder 002:091)
- Earl Estabrook to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 September 14 (Box-folder 002:092)
- Ray H. Corbett to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 September 15 (Box-folder 002:093)
- A. L. Bryon-Curtiss to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 September 26 (Box-folder 002:094)
- Meredith B. Wood to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 September 29 (Box-folder 002:095)
- E. Lab. Cherbonnier to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 September 30 (Box-folder 002:096)
- Margaret Lockwood to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 October 11 (Box-folder 002:097)
- Joseph P. Verdery to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 October 11 (Box-folder 002:098)
- Donald R. Woodward to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 October 12 (Box-folder 002:099)
- Judy Crawford to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 October 20 (Box-folder 002:100)
- James Luther Adams to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 November 15 (Box-folder 002:101)
- Judson D. Howard to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 November 18 (Box-folder 002:102)
- Ann Linder and Howie Reynolds to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 November 21 (Box-folder 002:103)
- Donald G. Lothrop to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 November 28 (Box-folder 002:104)
- Simon Doniger to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 December 12 (Box-folder 002:105)
- David R. Hunter to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 December 13 (Box-folder 002:106)
- Howard Selsam to Joseph Fletcher, 1955 December 29 (Box-folder 002:107)
- Calendar for Boston State Hospital Curriculum: Religion for Psychiatrists, [1955] (Box-folder 002:108)
- Avis De Voto to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, [1955] (Box-folder 002:109)
- Edmond Cahn to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 January 4 (Box-folder 002:110)
- Edmond Cahn to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 January 6 (Box-folder 002:111)
- Abraham H. Maslow to [Hette] de Forest; Hette de Forest to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 January 6, 1 item (Box-folder 002:112)
- James F. Meeker to Friend, 1956 January 20 (Box-folder 002:113)
- John to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 January 26 (Box-folder 002:114)
- David J. McVey to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 February 3 (Box-folder 002:115)
- Angus D. to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 February 3 (Box-folder 002:116)
- George L. Niles to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 February 4 (Box-folder 002:117)
- Paul and Edna Coste to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1956 [February] (Box-folder 002:118)
- Ann [Linder] and Howie [Reynolds] to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 March 1 (Box-folder 002:119)
- [ ] to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1956 March 5 (Box-folder 002:120)
- Marian Repper to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 March 6 (Box-folder 002:121)
- Colin R. Campbell to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 March 12 (Box-folder 002:122)
- A. L. Byron-Curtiss to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, 1956 March 14 (Box-folder 002:123)
- Warren Rempel to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 March 15 (Box-folder 002:124)
- W. H. McKenna to Forrest and Joseph Fletcher, 1956 March 17 (Box-folder 002:125)
- Seward Hiltner to Joseph Fletcher, [1956] March 29 (Box-folder 002:126)
- Arnold Nash to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 April 10 (Box-folder 002:127)
- Edward Gallahue to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 April 18 (Box-folder 002:128)
- Seward Hiltner to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 May 14 (Box-folder 002:129)
- Nathaniel N. Noble to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 May 14 (Box-folder 002:130)
- Gavin Scott to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 May 16 (Box-folder 002:131)
- William Wolf to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 July 4 (Box-folder 003:001)
- Woody Sif[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 July 11 (Box-folder 003:002)
- Ralph Lord Roy to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 July 12 (Box-folder 003:003)
- Raymond W. Albright to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 July 17 (Box-folder 003:004)
- Gordon C. Graham to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 August 3 (Box-folder 003:005)
- Pauline to Joseph Fletcher, 1956 August 15 (Box-folder 003:006)
- Nan to Forrest and Joseph Fletcher, 1956 August 20 (Box-folder 003:007)
- Fred to Joseph Fletcher, [1956] December 23 (Box-folder 003:008)
- Maurice and Aimee Leihitt to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1957 January 9 (Box-folder 003:009)
- Richard R. Gay to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 July 5 (Box-folder 003:010)
- Elizabeth [McKenna] to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 August 26 (Box-folder 003:011)
- Cyril E. Hudson to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 August 30 (Box-folder 003:012)
- Charles Wesley Lowry to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 September 25 (Box-folder 003:013)
- George Abbe to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 October 18 (Box-folder 003:014)
- Bill to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 October 22 (Box-folder 003:015)
- Alice M. Kuhn to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 October 27 (Box-folder 003:016)
- John Charles Wynn to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 October 29 (Box-folder 003:017)
- Richard R. Gay to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 November 26 (Box-folder 003:018)
- Brad to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 December 18 (Box-folder 003:019)
- Bradford Johnson to Joseph Fletcher, 1957 December 20 (Box-folder 003:020)
- Florence H. Luscomb to [Joseph Fletcher], 1957 December 28 (Box-folder 003:021)
- Chad Walsh to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 January 14 (Box-folder 003:022)
- Gordon T. Charlton, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 February 17 (Box-folder 003:023)
- E. L. Malone, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 February 18 (Box-folder 003:024)
- Dick Reid to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 February 24 (Box-folder 003:025)
- Cyril C. Means, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 February 26 (Box-folder 003:026)
- Whitney Hale to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 March 14 (Box-folder 003:027)
- Cyril E. Hudson to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 March 14 (Box-folder 003:028)
- Fostee Pete Nauffts to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 March 19 (Box-folder 003:029)
- Jocko to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 March 19 (Box-folder 003:030)
- Kenneth W. Warren to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1958 (Box-folder 003:031)
- Thomas M. Wade III to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 April 18 (Box-folder 003:032)
- Cyril E. Hudson to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 April 29 (Box-folder 003:033)
- Glenn Matthew White to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 May 5 (Box-folder 003:034)
- Ralph Harper to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 May 6 (Box-folder 003:035)
- Thomas N. Dabney to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 May 7 (Box-folder 003:036)
- Anson P. S. to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 June 9 (Box-folder 003:037)
- Powel to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 July 21 (Box-folder 003:038)
- Charles V. Gerkin to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 September 5 (Box-folder 003:039)
- [Hawed] to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 September 12 (Box-folder 003:040)
- Shinichi Inoue to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 September 20 (Box-folder 003:041)
- Richard C. Shaw to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 October 28 (Box-folder 003:042)
- Herbert Gezork to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 November 14 (Box-folder 003:043)
- Arthur E. Walmsley to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 December 17 (Box-folder 003:044)
- George [Ross?] to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 December 18 (Box-folder 003:045)
- Gerald F. Gilmore to Joseph Fletcher, 1958 December 19 (Box-folder 003:046)
- John Crocker, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 January 7 (Box-folder 003:047)
- Jack to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 January 9 (Box-folder 003:048)
- John Crocker, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 January 15 (Box-folder 003:049)
- P. Ken Imai to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 January 20 (Box-folder 003:050)
- W. Owings Stone to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 January 20 (Box-folder 003:051)
- William Howard Melish to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 January 29 (Box-folder 003:052)
- Herbert Gezork to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 February 11 (Box-folder 003:053)
- Richard R. Rowe to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 February 27 (Box-folder 003:054)
- Timo Thy Iwai to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 March 27 (Box-folder 003:055)
- George Cosson to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 March 31 (Box-folder 003:056)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 1 (Box-folder 003:057)
- George Cosson to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 8 (Box-folder 003:058)
- Joseph Fletcher to George Cosson [copy], 1959 April 14 (Box-folder 003:059)
- Charles V. Harris to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 14 (Box-folder 003:060)
- George Cosson to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 15 (Box-folder 003:061)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 16 (Box-folder 003:062)
- [Guy Emery Shipler] to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 21 (Box-folder 003:063)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 23 (Box-folder 003:064)
- John A. T. Robinson to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 26 (Box-folder 003:065)
- Richard M. Fagley to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1959 April 28 (Box-folder 003:066)
- E. A. Vastyan to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 May 1 (Box-folder 003:067)
- Frederick J. Warnecke to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 May 11 (Box-folder 003:068)
- W. Bradford Patterson to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 May 22 (Box-folder 003:069)
- Yasutaro Danno to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 May 31 (Box-folder 003:070)
- Arnold Purdie to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 June 9 (Box-folder 003:071)
- Richard Nixon to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 June 18 (Box-folder 003:072)
- Peter Day to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 July 2 (Box-folder 003:073)
- Katharine A[ ] Merrill to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 July 8 (Box-folder 003:074)
- Gibson Winter to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 July 14 (Box-folder 003:075)
- George Albert Smith to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 July 20 (Box-folder 003:076)
- Paul Donham to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 July 22 (Box-folder 003:077)
- Thomas K. Thompson to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 July 22 (Box-folder 003:078)
- Richard H. Wilmer, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 July 27 (Box-folder 003:079)
- Wedding Speech for Rene Stephan Tillich and Mary Ruth Wild, 1959 August 8 (Box-folder 003:080)
- Rollins B. V. [to Joseph Fletcher], 1959 August 12 (Box-folder 003:081)
- Form letter and card for John Robinson, Bishop of Woolwich, 1959 September, 2 items (Box-folder 003:082)
- Roy G. Demarsh to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 October 15 (Box-folder 003:083)
- Madeline Gray to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 October 27 (Box-folder 003:084)
- Edmond [Cahn] to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 October 28 (Box-folder 003:085)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 November 4 (Box-folder 003:086)
- Stanley Plattenburg to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 November 4 (Box-folder 003:087)
- Edmund Cahn to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 November 5 (Box-folder 003:088)
- Joseph Fletcher to Guy Brown [copy], 1959 November 16 (Box-folder 003:089)
- Ed Day to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 November 19 (Box-folder 003:090)
- James Hennessy to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure and related items, 1959 November 19, 6 items (Box-folder 003:091)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 November 20 (Box-folder 003:092)
- Edmond to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 November 23 (Box-folder 003:093)
- Alan F. Guttmacher to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 November 25 (Box-folder 003:094)
- A. J. Jackson to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 3 (Box-folder 003:095)
- George E. Wiltbank to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 3 (Box-folder 003:096)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 4 (Box-folder 003:097)
- Richard W. Duesenberg to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 7 (Box-folder 003:098)
- Ruth Bettman to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 8 (Box-folder 003:099)
- Madeline Gray to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 8 (Box-folder 003:100)
- Samuel S. Ruderman to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 10 (Box-folder 003:101)
- Hikaru Yanagihara to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 13 (Box-folder 003:102)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 14 (Box-folder 003:103)
- Charles L. Taylor to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 18 (Box-folder 003:104)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 (Box-folder 003:105)
- William Stringfellow to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 23 (Box-folder 003:106)
- Edward E. Thornton to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 23 (Box-folder 003:107)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 30 (Box-folder 003:108)
- Bob McNair to Joseph Fletcher, 1959 December 30 (Box-folder 003:109)
- Giles B. Gunn to Joseph Fletcher, [1959] (Box-folder 003:110)
- [W. H. McKenna] to Joseph Fletcher, [1959] (Box-folder 003:111)
- Membership Card for the Twenty Club, 1959 (Box-folder 003:112)
- Paul to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] February 4 (Box-folder 004:001)
- Elsie Lyon to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] February 8 (Box-folder 004:002)
- Jerome Davis to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] February 20 (Box-folder 004:003)
- Harold to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] February 23 (Box-folder 004:004)
- Joseph Fletcher to Hugh Weston, [with Weston's response], [1950s] April 20 (Box-folder 004:005)
- Constance Daniels to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s April] (Box-folder 004:006)
- Bink Young to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] July 18 (Box-folder 004:007)
- John to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] September 25 (Box-folder 004:008)
- Anonymous Note, [1950s] October 22 (Box-folder 004:009)
- Alice N. Proskauer to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] October 24 (Box-folder 004:010)
- David P. Ellms to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] November 7 (Box-folder 004:011)
- Paul to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] November 23 (Box-folder 004:012)
- Amy Weden [Mrs. David B. Wilson] to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] November 23 (Box-folder 004:013)
- Peter O'Connell to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] November 28 (Box-folder 004:014)
- Brigid to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] December 12 (Box-folder 004:015)
- L. B. Naylor to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, [1950s] December (Box-folder 004:016)
- Jocko to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, [1950s December] (Box-folder 004:017)
- [Jane Fletcher] to [Joseph Fletcher], [1950s] (Box-folder 004:018)
- Yuan Francois to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:019)
- Peggy King to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:020)
- Anne Swett to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:021)
- Mary [McFarlane] Walker to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:022)
- J. Craig R. Wright to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s (Box-folder 004:023)
- April to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:024)
- Bill to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:025)
- Ed to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:026)
- Molle to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:027)
- Pzp to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:028)
- Ruthie to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:029)
- Ruthie to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:030)
- Thelina to Joseph Fletcher, [1950s] (Box-folder 004:031)
- David E. Smith to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 January 2 (Box-folder 004:032)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure 1960, 2 items (Box-folder 004:033)
- Eva Chang to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 January 12 (Box-folder 004:034)
- William Stringfellow to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 January 12 (Box-folder 004:035)
- Robert B. Mason to Joseph Fletcher, [1960] January 24 (Box-folder 004:036)
- Conrad H. Gesner to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 January 25 (Box-folder 004:037)
- Gordon Hubel to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 January 26 (Box-folder 004:038)
- W. Wesley Konrad to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 February 3 (Box-folder 004:039)
- Walter M. Higley to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 February 4 (Box-folder 004:040)
- C. Kenneth Sansbury to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 February 12 (Box-folder 004:041)
- Edward E. Thornton to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 February 17 (Box-folder 004:042)
- Ralente Bat[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 March 3 (Box-folder 004:043)
- Mary E. Hudson to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1960 March 6 (Box-folder 004:044)
- Bob Woodroofe to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 March 14 (Box-folder 004:045)
- Burke Rivers to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 March 21 (Box-folder 004:046)
- Edwin W. Grilley, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 March 29 (Box-folder 004:047)
- James H. Burns to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 April 4 (Box-folder 004:048)
- George Johnston and E. Clifford St[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 April 13 (Box-folder 004:049)
- George Easter to Joe [Joseph Fletcher] and Forrest [Fletcher], with enclosure, 1960 April 29 (Box-folder 004:050)
- Harold to [Joseph Fletcher], 1960 [April] (Box-folder 004:051)
- Roddey and Caroline to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1960 May 1 (Box-folder 004:052)
- Alfonso Rodriguez to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 May 2 (Box-folder 004:053)
- Joseph G. Moore to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 May 17 (Box-folder 004:054)
- Frank B. Sayre, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 May 27 (Box-folder 004:055)
- Ogden Hoffman to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 June 9 (Box-folder 004:056)
- William B. Spofford to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 June 9 (Box-folder 004:057)
- John a. Sanford to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 June 14 (Box-folder 004:058)
- Wilfred Myll to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 July 13 (Box-folder 004:059)
- Richard A. Strong to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 August 30 (Box-folder 004:060)
- Richard Morford to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 september 9 (Box-folder 004:061)
- Nicholas B. Phelps to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 September 16 (Box-folder 004:062)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 September 19 (Box-folder 004:063)
- Massey H. Shepherd, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 September 21 (Box-folder 004:064)
- George H. Easter to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 September 24 (Box-folder 004:065)
- H. B. W. to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 October 13 (Box-folder 004:066)
- Jeff to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 October 13 (Box-folder 004:067)
- Paul Swain Havens to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 October 21 (Box-folder 004:068)
- William A. Coolidge to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1960 October 31, 2 Items (Box-folder 004:069)
- Charles A. M. Hall to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 October 31 (Box-folder 004:070)
- Jack to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 2 (Box-folder 004:071)
- John Ribble to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 3 (Box-folder 004:072)
- Walt Oakley to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 7 (Box-folder 004:073)
- to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 10 (Box-folder 004:074)
- Judy P[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 15 (Box-folder 004:075)
- Deane William Ferm to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 18 (Box-folder 004:076)
- Robert J. McCloskey to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 18 (Box-folder 004:077)
- Bill [William Howard Melish] to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 21 (Box-folder 004:078)
- Forrest Fletcher to Julia [Fletcher], 1960 November 22 (Box-folder 004:079)
- Lewis N. Lukens to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 22 (Box-folder 004:080)
- William Howard Melish to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 November 30 (Box-folder 004:081)
- Bob Geniesse to Joseph Fletcher, [1960 November] (Box-folder 004:082)
- James M. Lichliter to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 December 2 (Box-folder 004:083)
- Charles B. T[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 December 2 (Box-folder 004:084)
- Amory Houghton, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 December 5 (Box-folder 004:085)
- B. Loring Young to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 December 5 (Box-folder 004:086)
- Arthur E. Sutherland to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 December 6 (Box-folder 004:087)
- Cliff Stanley to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 December 12 (Box-folder 004:088)
- Paul A. Bankston to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 December 13 (Box-folder 004:089)
- F. V. H. Carthy to Joseph Fletcher, 1960 December 13 (Box-folder 004:090)
- John [Gould] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1960 December 16 (Box-folder 004:091)
- Catherine Cunningham to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1960 December 30 (Box-folder 004:092)
- American Society of Christian Social Ethics Membership Card for Joseph Fletcher, 1960 (Box-folder 004:093)
- Comment on Joseph Fletcher's "New Look in Christian Ethics," by Harry Davis, ca. 1960 (Box-folder 004:094)
- [Jane Fletcher] to Forrest, Joseph Sr., and Joseph Fletcher, Jr., [1960] (Box-folder 004:095)
- Julia Fletcher to Joseph Fletcher and family, [1960] (Box-folder 004:096)
- George Easter to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 January 21 (Box-folder 004:097)
- John C. W. Linsley to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 February 8 (Box-folder 004:098)
- James A. Pike to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 February 13 (Box-folder 004:099)
- Scott P to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 February 14 (Box-folder 004:100)
- John C. W. Linsley to Henrique Todt, 1961 February 16 (Box-folder 004:101)
- Walter G. Muelder to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 February 28 (Box-folder 004:102)
- Eliot White to [Joseph Fletcher], 1961 March 6 (Box-folder 004:103)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to John, 1961 April 28 (Box-folder 004:104)
- Thomas J. Devine to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 July 13 (Box-folder 004:105)
- Allen W. Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 August 28 (Box-folder 004:106)
- Beatrice McClintock to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 September 1 (Box-folder 004:107)
- Barbara Williams to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 September 5 (Box-folder 004:108)
- Edward [Cahn?] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1961 September 7 (Box-folder 004:109)
- Jones B. Shannon to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 September 15 (Box-folder 004:110)
- John L. Hazard to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 September 25 (Box-folder 004:111)